

# **PROFILE**

I am 25 years old. I am the breadwinner of my family. I have no problem with exploring new programming languages. I am a fast learner and will be able to adapt to any environment. I love opportunities where I'll be able to grow and experience new things in life.

# CONTACT

PHONE: +63 928 451 9423

WEBSITE:

https://github.com/daikkin

**EMAIL:** 

reancyvillacarlos@gmail.com

### **HOBBIES**

Chess
Computer Games
Learn new Programming Languages

# REANCY VILLACARLOS

Software/Web Developer

## **EDUCATION**

### Cebu Technological University - Main Campus

June, 2015 - May, 2019

Bachelor of Science in Information and Communication Technology

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

### Freelance Developer Software/Web Developer

January, 2021-present

Worked as a Freelance/Outsource Developer, using any programming languages depending on requirement.

### **MET Philippines Web Developer**

October, 2021-September, 2022

Worked on various web applications using PHP (Laravel framework).

### MedSpecialized, Inc. Software Developer

November 2019-January 2021

Worked on a Medical Software using PowerBuilder and other tools.

### RightApps Solutions and Services Software/Web Developer

December 2018-June 2019

Worked on Reservation System, Accounting System, HR & Payroll System, Inventory System. Used C#, PHP (Laravel Framework), JavaScript (with libraries), MySQL and PostgreSQL.

### **SKILLS**

